1. comment("Story: Book an appointment")
5. comment("Given that the user has logged into their account")
9. openBrowser(G_SiteURL)
15. This for visual test and you use Take Screenshot as a checkpoint
19. callTestCase(findTestCase("Common Test Cases/Login"), ["Username":"John Doe", "Password":"ThisIsNotAPassword"], STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. click(findTestObject("Page_CuraHomepage/btn_MakeAppointment"))
5. setText(findTestObject("Page_Login/txt_UserName"), Username)
9. setText(findTestObject("Page_Login/txt_Password"), Password)
13. click(findTestObject("Page_Login/btn_Login"))
17. landingPage = verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/div_Appointment"), G_Timeout)
23. comment("And Appointment page is displayed")
27. if (true)
1. takeScreenshotAsCheckpoint("appointment page")
5. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/lst_Facility"), "Hongkong CURA Healthcare Center", false)
9. check(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/chk_Medicaid"))
13. check(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/chk_Readmission"))
17. setText(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/txt_VisitDate"), "27/12/2016")
21. setText(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/txt_Comment"), "Please make appointment as soon as possible.")
31. comment("When he fills in valid information in Appointment page")
35. click(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/btn_BookAppointment"))
39. verifyTextPresent("Appointment Confirmation", false)
43. comment("Then he should be able to book a new appointment")
47. if (true)
1. takeFullPageScreenshotAsCheckpoint("booked appointment", [findTestObject("Page_AppointmentConfirmation/lbl_VisitDate")])